<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Boards on Omega Psi at JHU</title>
    <link>https://OmegaPsiJHU.github.io/board/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Boards on Omega Psi at JHU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 09:54:40 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://OmegaPsiJHU.github.io/board/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kiley McKee</title>
      <link>https://OmegaPsiJHU.github.io/board/kiley-mckee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 09:54:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OmegaPsiJHU.github.io/board/kiley-mckee/</guid>
      <description>Kiley is a sophomore Cognitive Science and Psychology double major at Johns Hopkins University. She is currently working on a project involving spatial thinking and 3rd grade STEM curriculum development with Hopkins&amp;rsquo; Science of Learning Institute. In the future, Kiley hopes to continue bridging the gap between science of learning research and education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anne Li</title>
      <link>https://OmegaPsiJHU.github.io/board/anne-li/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 14:03:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OmegaPsiJHU.github.io/board/anne-li/</guid>
      <description>Anne is a senior at the Johns Hopkins University double majoring in neuroscience and Spanish on a pre-medical track. Her research interests include using microRNAs as a potential source of therapy for diseases, especially neurological diseases and brain cancers. She is currently working with microRNAs and glioblastoma. Her aim is to achieve an MD-PhD and work in pediatric neurology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jane Brusilovsky</title>
      <link>https://OmegaPsiJHU.github.io/board/jane-brusilovsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 09:54:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OmegaPsiJHU.github.io/board/jane-brusilovsky/</guid>
      <description>Jane is a junior majoring in Cognitive Science with focal areas in linguistics and neuroscience. She researches PTSD, schizophrenia, bipolar disorder at LIBD. She is a Wilson Fellow who is studying the 3D printing of stroke legions. Following college, she plans on attending medical school to pursue her aspiration of becoming a surgeon and eventually working at a teaching hospital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angela Wang</title>
      <link>https://OmegaPsiJHU.github.io/board/angela-wang/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 12:53:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OmegaPsiJHU.github.io/board/angela-wang/</guid>
      <description>Angela is a senior majoring in public health and psychology. Her research interests are clinical and cognitive psychology. She loves to watch Netflix and korean dramas in her free time and is excited to contribute more to Omega Psi this semester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coleman Haley</title>
      <link>https://OmegaPsiJHU.github.io/board/coleman-haley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 21:56:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OmegaPsiJHU.github.io/board/coleman-haley/</guid>
      <description>Coleman is a junior majoring in computer science and cognitive science with focal areas in linguistics and computational approaches to cognition. He is interested in computational models of language and interpretable machine learning. He works with Dr. Colin Wilson in the phonology lab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karen Wang</title>
      <link>https://OmegaPsiJHU.github.io/board/karen-wang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 09:54:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OmegaPsiJHU.github.io/board/karen-wang/</guid>
      <description>Karen is a junior majoring in Cognitive Science on the pre-medical track. She researches the neural mechanisms of addiction behavior and is interested in the various responses of the brain to reward expectations. Following college, she plans on attending medical school and work in neurology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>